ssww.com 2007-12-29

# Your Privacy & Security : S&S Worldwide

Web Favorites

Shop By Category

Our Customers Say

"I love S&S®! We have been purchasing all of our colored paper, paint, and class packs from S&S® for over 20 years. Their products, delivery time, and customer service have always been exceptional. S&S® pricing is highly competitive. Colorsplash! paint and construction paper have been a favorite here. The colors are consistently bright and vivid."

Marjorie G.

"Your craft kits are a lifesaver for my programs!"

Shirley B.

| 

**Your Privacy & Security**

S&S Worldwide is committed to providing both customers and visitors with the utmost in privacy and security. We abide by all industry guidelines and consistently monitor our management and methods in order to maintain our valued reputation and integrity. This is our promise to our customers, clients, affiliate partners and property users. This privacy statement discloses our privacy practices for www.ssww.com for the purpose of demonstrating our commitment to your privacy. 

**Information Collection and Use**

S&S Worldwide is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

**Inquiries, Forms and Online Transactions**

The S&S Worldwide Web site is designed to attract customers interested in taking advantage of the great prices and excellent quality of our products. The site has several forms available to our customers and visitors that ask for Personal Identifiable Information. These include Requests for Information, Catalog Requests, Newsletter Subscription, Activity Guides downloads, etc. Any information requested by the forms and any future communication resulting from the information disclosed therein shall be directly related to the user's request. 

The site also has an Online Order Form that enables our customers to place an order online. S&S Worldwide uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting certain kinds of information, such as credit card payment information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of most browsers window during SSL transactions that involve credit cards and other forms of payment. Any time S&S Worldwide asks you for a credit card number for payment or for verification purposes, it will be SSL encrypted. The information you provide will be stored securely on our servers. Once you choose to store or enter your credit card number on S&S Worldwide, it will not be displayed back to you in its entirety when you retrieve or edit it in the future. Instead of the entire number, you will only see asterisks and either the first four digits or the last four digits of your number. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Personally Identifiable Information is information that can be used to identify a specific user. In the course of filling out an inquiry, requesting a catalog or making a purchase online, you may be asked to disclose Personal Identifiable Information. S&S Worldwide will never collect information from you without your permission. Specifically, you may be asked to provide one or more of the following: 

Name   
Postal address   
Phone number   
Email address   
Company name   
Credit Card Number 

Providing personally identifiable information is strictly voluntary. It may, however, be necessary for you to provide the information requested in order for S&S to process your request and or purchase. Whenever a customer or a visitor provides Personal Identifiable Information it will be provided via a secured connection (SSL). 

**Visitors**

S&S Worldwide does not require personal information from visitors using our Web site to view our great line of products. 

**Newsletter**

Customers and visitors may register to receive our monthly newsletter in order to be notified of new offers and special discounts. When you register for our newsletter certain information will be requested from you to include but not limited to name, city/state, email address, etc. Your name and email address will not be shared, sold, rented nor made public (see "Sharing" below). If at any time you do not wish to continue to receive our monthly newsletter, you can opt-out of our newsletter by sending us an email at listmgr@ssww.com. 

**Legal**

As a rule, S&S Worldwide will not intentionally disclose personally identifiable information about its Web site users to any third party without first receiving the user's permission. However, S&S Worldwide may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to, (a) conform to edicts of law or comply with legal process, (b) protect and defend the rights or property of S&S Worldwide, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of any user of S&S Worldwide Programs. 

**Cookies**

We use "cookies" on our website. Cookies are pieces of information that an Internet site transfers to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them almost everywhere on the Internet. S&S Worldwide uses cookies to recognize visitors when they return to our sites. Once we know it's you, we can customize your online visit. For instance, when you are ready to purchase an item, a cookie allows our site to "remember" you have added the item to your shopping cart. 

We can also show you new products based on your preferences, alert you to new website features, or tell you what new products we have. We may also evaluate our content and services and tailor our websites, for visitors, based on other information we collect such as IP addresses, which are numbers assigned to your computer whenever you use the Internet, pixel tags (or clear gifs), and the type of Internet browser or operating system you are using. This information is collected in the aggregate, but we may tie it to your personal information through cookie use as described above. 

Our company contracts under the confidentiality restrictions mentioned above with Coremetrics, a service partner, to provide data collection and reports regarding our customers' activities on our site. Coremetrics may use cookies on our behalf and may receive information about your browsing and buying activity. Coremetrics may store member ID, city, state, zip code, and email address on our behalf. Under no circumstances may Coremetrics use your information other than in connection with providing services to us to make our site more useful and efficient. If you would like to opt out of these particular services, please click here. 

**Sharing**

S&S Worldwide may share aggregated Non-Personally Identifiable Information with our affiliates partners, business partners, and prospective business partners. Such information is shared only for marketing purposes. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person, natural or juridical. 

**Links**

Our Web site contains links to variety of other sites that provide resource information. Please be aware that S&S Worldwide is responsible only for the privacy practices of our Web site. Other Web sites, to which we link, have their own specific privacy policies. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected via S&S Worldwide. 

**Spam Complaints**

S&S Worldwide is 100% permission based! 

If you are receiving e-mails or newsletters from S&S Worldwide you have opted-in to receive such e-mails or newsletters. Spam complaints concerning S&S Worldwide lists are handled with the utmost scrutiny and promptness. If you have received e-mail(s) that you believe to be unsolicited, your e-mail address will be removed from the list to which you were subscribed, and you will not receive any further e-mail correspondence from us, unless otherwise requested in writing. S&S Worldwide upholds its belief in your privacy in order to maintain our valued reputation and integrity. 

Please note that if you have opted-in to receive information from an affiliate site, you must contact that site directly to be removed from their list. S&S Worldwide Affiliate Partners are prohibited to utilize spam as a marketing tool to promote our products. If you have received unsolicited email from one of our Affiliate Partners we ask that you notify us so that we can take appropriate action. You are welcomed to review our rules regarding affiliates and the use of spam to promote our products. If you have any questions or concerns about anything in this section, please contact us at privacy@ssww.com. 

**Security**

The S&S Worldwide Web site takes every reasonable precaution to protect our user's information. When you submit information via S&S Worldwide, your information is protected both on-line and off-line in accordance with applicable laws, regulations, and industry standards. For example, with out limitation, S&S Worldwide uses a full-time Network Administrator, SSL servers, PGP, and 128 bit data encryption to protect the confidentiality of the information you provide. If you have any questions about the security at our Web site, you can send an email to privacy@ssww.com. 

**Updating**

Correcting, updating, or requesting the deletion of information that you have provided may be accomplished by e-mailing privacy@ssww.com, or by writing S&S Worldwide Privacy Policy, 75 Mill Street, P.O. Box 513, Colchester, CT 06415-0513. 

**Notification of Changes**

S&S Worldwide fundamental commitment to protecting customer privacy will not change. However, regulatory changes or other circumstances may require us to modify this Security and Privacy Statement. In the event that we do amend this statement, it will be posted at www.ssww.com/privacy and will be effective 15 days after is it posted. Please note that S&S Worldwide will not change the usage of personally identifiable information collected under a privacy statement without first obtaining express user permission via e-mail. S&S Worldwide policy is to use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If you would like to submit questions or concerns regarding this Security and Privacy Statement, you should e-mail privacy@ssww.com, or write S&S Worldwide, Security and Privacy Policy, 75 Mill Street, P.O. Box 513, Colchester, CT 06415-0513. 

|   
---|---|---
